b2bj.com 2005-03-07

# b2bSites.com - Add / Modify URL

**b2bSites.com Privacy Policy**

As a result of the World Wide Web continually evolving with new technologies, security features and technologies, this Policy will change from time to time. b2bSites.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time without formal notice to you. 

Our current privacy policy practices will be accessible through the posting of a clear and conspicuous link near the bottom of most b2bSites.com web pages. Please review our Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Service policy on a regular basis so that you will be apprised of any changes. 

**What does b2bSites.com Privacy Policy cover?**

This Privacy Policy applies to collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by b2bSites.com. Please be aware that as part of our "Services", b2bSites.com provides search results and links to Web sites operated by third parties. b2bSites.com is not responsible for the information collection, applications, privacy practices or content of those third party Web sites. 

**b2bSites.com uses cookies.**

Like many sites, b2bSites.com collects information about online behavior using cookies. To b2bSites.com, using information with cookies is an anonymous way to survey how we are doing and to look for ways to improve our Services. These cookies contain identification information that enables us to see how our users are interacting with our site. This allows us to better streamline and personalize the experiences associated with using our site. 

Cookies also allow us to know about repeat visitors and if we are delivering quality products and services. b2bSites.com may also use cookies to identify sites our repeat visitors are coming from, so that we can place more of our online advertising on these sites. 

You may set your browser software to reject cookies, but you may not be able to use all of the features of the Services. 

**What information does b2bSites.com collect and how is it used? Does B2bSites.com disclose information to third parties?**

b2bSites.com collects traffic and usage that is not personally identifying or identifiable, and is not supplemented or combined with personally identifying or identifiable information. b2bSites.com may share information about usage of the Services with third parties, but only in aggregated, anonymous form. For example, we may tell an advertiser or content provider how many people visit our site or certain areas within our Web site, or what search terms are most popular. 

b2bSites.com also collects some information regarding use of the Services by observing browser functions and the files (pages) that users access. For example, b2bSites.com's servers collect information about the specific page you entered in order to enable b2bSites.com to better determine how our traffic is obtained. 

**Is data stored or obtained by b2bSites.com secure?**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, b2bSites.com has put in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information it collects online. However, data security is a constantly evolving art and science. You should consider any communication that you transmit to b2bSites.com (such as data, questions or answers, comments, or suggestions) as non-confidential, and agree that b2bSites.com will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to you is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient. 

**Additional questions**

Please use our contact form with any additional questions that you may have.
